export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Nasal administration enters through the:",
    options: ['Mouth', 'Skin', 'Nose', 'Vein'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Subcutaneous injection is given under the:",
    options: ['Bone', 'Skin', 'Muscle', 'Artery'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Liver plays a major role in drug:",
    options: ['Taste', 'Elimination', 'Color change', 'Storage only'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Tetracaine is classified as:",
    options: ['Ester', 'Amide', 'Opioid', 'Barbiturate'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Lidocaine belongs to which group?",
    options: ['Esters', 'Amides', 'Opioids', 'Steroids'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Nitrous oxide provides:",
    options: ['General anesthesia', 'Antibiotic action', 'Vitamin supply', 'Hormone therapy'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Propofol IV is used to induce:",
    options: ['Analgesia only', 'Unconsciousness', 'Muscle growth', 'Antibiotic effect'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Meperidine is mainly used for:",
    options: ['Analgesia', 'Muscle relaxation', 'Sedation only', 'Antibiotic'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Ketamine can provide:",
    options: ['Analgesia', 'Antifungal effect', 'Diuretic action', 'Antacid'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Inhalation agents are usually combined with:",
    options: ['Nothing', 'IV drugs', 'Food', 'Exercise'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Age is important in preoperative:",
    options: ['Evaluation', 'Decoration', 'Entertainment', 'Marketing'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "BP monitoring means checking:",
    options: ['Blood pressure', 'Body pain', 'Brain power', 'Breathing power'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Renal function refers to the:",
    options: ['Heart', 'Kidney', 'Liver', 'Lung'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Anesthesia controls pain during:",
    options: ['Operation', 'Breakfast', 'Study', 'Driving'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Gut participates in drug:",
    options: ['Elimination', 'Color', 'Smell', 'Sound'],
    answer: 0
  },
];